Guide to the Picture File, 1600s-1979 and undated, bulk 1814-1950
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- Socialist Party Records Series, 1800s-1983, (5 boxes)
  - People Subseries, 1800s-1970, 1900s and undated
    - McReynolds, Dave, 1956 June 8-10, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M436)
    - McVickers, Mary, 1900s, (2 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M437)
    - Merrill, Herbert M., 1934, (postcard) (Folder M438)
    - Mette, John Allen, 1900s, (card photograph) (Folder M439)
    - Miscellany, A-W, 1936, 1956 June 8-10, and 1900s, (8 black-and-white photographs and 1 postcard) (Box 14, Folder M440.1)
    - Miscellany, A-W, 1900s, (5 black-and-white photographs, 1 card photograph and 1 postcard) (Folder M440.2)
    - Miscellany, A-W, 1924, 1934, and 1900s, (8 black-and-white photographs, 1 card photograph and 1 postcard) (Folder M440.3)
    - Miscellany, A-W, 1942 May 27, 1956 June 8-10 and 1900s, (4 black-and-white photographs, 2 handbills, 1 black-and-white photographic illustration, and 2 postcards (Folder M440.4)
    - Miscellany, A-W, 1956 June 8-10, 1954 and 1900s, (7 black-and-white photographs, 1 card photograph and 2 postcards) (Folder M440.5)
    - Miscellany, A-W, 1913 Mar., circa 1936, and 1900s, (8 black-and-white photographs and 3 card photographs) (Folder M440.6)
    - Miscellany, A-W, 1926 Sept., 1933, and 1900s, (10 black-and-white photographs and 1 postcard) (Folder M440.7)
    - Miscellany, A-W, 1956 June 8-10, 1954, and 1900s, (1 black-and-white photograph, 1 black-and-white photographic illustration, 2 card photographs,1 duotone plate and 1 postcard) (Folder M440.8)
    - Mitchell, Henry Leland, 1934 and 1948, (2 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M441)
      A photographic illustration was removed to OV41 in the Oversize Subseries.
    - Mitchell, Henry Leland, 1970 Apr. 14, (black-and-white photographic illustration)
      Removed from M441 to the Oversize Series.
    - Mooney, Tom, 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M442)
    - Motley, Sidney W., 1900s, (2 card photographs) (Folder M443)
    - Murray, Pauli, 1900s, (2 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M444)
    - Murray, Philip and James B. Carey, 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M445)
    - Myers, Robin, 1900s, (7 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M446)
    - Myers, Robin and Samuel Friedman, 1956 June 8-10 and 1900s, (2 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M447)
    - National Executive Committee, 1920s, circa 1920s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M448)
    - National Executive Committee, Otto Branstetter, 1920, 1920, (3 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M449)
      One negative removed to N8 in the Negatives Series.
    - National Executive Committee, Otto Branstetter, 1920, 1920, (negative)
      Removed to the Negatives Series from M449.
    - National Executive Committee, Social Democratic Party, 1900, 1900, (card photograph)
      One negative removed to N9 in the Negatives Series.
    - National Executive Committee, Social Democratic Party, 1900, 1900, (negative)
      Removed to the Negatives Series from OV42 in the Oversize Subseries.
    - National Office and Staff, Chicago, 1909, 1909, (1 black-and-white photograph and 2 card photographs) (Folder M450)
    - National Office and Staff, Chicago, circa 1920-1923, circa 1923, (card photograph) (Folder M451)
      A negative was removed to N10 in the Negatives Series.
    - National Office and Staff, Chicago, circa 1920-1923, circa 1920-1923, (negative)
      Removed to the Negatives Series from M451.
    - Nelson, George, 1934 and 1936, (3 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M452)
    - New York City Party (unidentified), 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M453)
    - New York, N.Y., 1957 Feb. 21, (3 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M454)
    - New York Party members, 1900s, (12 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M455)
    - New York State Office and staff, circa 1910, circa 1910, (card photograph) (Folder M456)
      One negative removed to N11 in the Negatives Series.
    - New York State Office and staff, circa 1910, circa 1910, (negative)
      Removed to the Negatives Series from M456.
    - Nkrumah, Kwame, 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M457)
    - O'Hagan, Walter, 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M458)
    - O'Hare, Kate Richards, 1900s, (5 black-and-white photographs and 1 clipping (Folder M459)
    - O'Neal, James, 1900s, (2 black-and-white photographs and 1 postcard) (Folder M460)
    - Packard, John C., 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M461)
    - Parker, Ben, 1956 June 8-10 and 1900s, (3 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M462)
    - Pauling, Linus, Aug. 1959 and 1900s, (mats) (Folder M463)
    - Perrin, E. W., circa 1910s and 1900s, (1 black-and-white photograph and 1 card photograph) (Folder M464)
    - Peters, Hans, 1956 June 8-10, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M465)
    - Porter, Paul, 1900s, (2 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M466)
    - Prevey, Marguerite, 1900s, (card photograph) (Folder M467)
    - Prison Comfort Club, 1920 and circa 1921, (2 card photographs) (Folder M468)
      2 negatives removed to N12 in the Negatives Series.
    - Prison Comfort Club, 1920 and circa 1921, (2 negatives)
      Removed to the Negatives Series from M468.
    - Randolph, Asa Philip, 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M469)
    - Rustin, Bayard and Charles S. Zimmerman, 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M470)
    - Rustin, Bayard and Charles S. Zimmerman, et al. at Socialist Party USA dinner, 1900s, (6 black-and-white contact sheets) (Folder M471)
    - Schechter, Max, 1948 Jan. 18, (2 handbills) (Box 15, Folder M472)
      These two handbills are duplicates.
    - Seidel, Emil, 1900s, (card photograph) (Folder M473)
    - Senior, Clarence O., 1900s, (1 black-and-white photograph and 2 black-and-white photographic illustrations) (Folder M474)
      One of the illustrations is a photocopy.
    - Sharts, Joseph W., 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M475)
    - Singer, Herman, 1956 June 8-10 and 1900s, (3 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M476)
    - Slayton, J. W., 1900s, (2 card photographs) (Folder M477)
    - Snyder, J. E., 1900s, (card photograph) (Folder M478)
    - "Socialist Unity Convention, Indianapolis, Ind., July 29-Aug. 1, 1901," undated, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M479)
    - Stedman, Seymour, 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M480)
      "See also Illinois Socialist Legislators."
    - Stone, Irving and Johnny Otis, 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M481)
    - Stone, Irving, Johnny Otis, and Russell Jacquet, 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M482)
    - Strikes - Unemployment, 1936 July 15 and 1900s, (6 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M483.1)
    - Strikes - Unemployment, 1919, 1946 Jan. 9, 11 and 1900s, (4 black-and-white photographs, 1 postcard and 1 black-and-white photographic illustration) (Folder M483.2)
    - Strikes - Unemployment, 1934 Feb. 11, 1960 Oct. 3 and 1900s, (6 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M483.3)
    - Strikes - Unemployment, 1946 Jan. 11-22, (6 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M483.4)
    - Strikes - Unemployment, 1938 and circa 1910, (3 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M483.5)
    - Thomas, Norman Mattoon (groups), circa 1936 and 1900s, (6 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M484.1)
    - Thomas, Norman Mattoon (groups), 1900s, (5 black-and-white photographs and 1 black-and-white photographic illustration) (Folder M484.2)
    - Thomas, Norman Mattoon (groups), 1949 Sept. 17, 1948, 1936 May 23 and 1900s, (6 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M484.3)
    - Thomas, Norman Mattoon (groups), circa 1936 and 1900s, (6 black-and-white photographs and 1 black-and-white photographic illustration) (Folder M484.4)
    - Thomas, Norman Mattoon (groups), 1964 and 1900s, (9 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M484.5)
    - Thomas, Norman Mattoon (groups), 1936 Jan., (6 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M484.6)
    - Thomas, Norman Mattoon (individual), 1926; 1935 May; circa 1940; and 1900s, (6 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M485.1)
    - Thomas, Norman Mattoon (individual), 1900s, (6 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M485.2)
    - Thomas, Norman Mattoon (individual), 1900s, (5 black-and-white photographs and 1 sketch) (Folder M485.3)
    - Thomas, Norman Mattoon (individual), 1936, 1944 Sept. 28, and 1900s, (6 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M485.4)
    - Thomas, Norman Mattoon (individual), 1900s, (4 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M485.5)
      Two card photographs and one black-and-white illustration removed to folder OV43, Box M01, in the Oversize Subseries.
    - Thomas, Norman Mattoon at Vietnam Day Teach-In - Berkeley, Cal., 1965 Mar. 22-23, (2 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M486)
      Both photographs have negatives available.
    - Tito, Josip Broz, 1956 Aug., (postcard) (Folder M487)
    - Trager, Frank, 1936 Dec., (1 black-and-white photograph and 1 postcard) (Folder M488)
    - Twining, Luella, undated, (1 card photograph and 1 black-and-white photograph) (Folder M489)
    - View of Norman Mattoon Thomas, 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M490)
    - Waldman, Louis, 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M491)
    - White, Bertha Hale, 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M492)
    - White, Daniel A., 1900s, (card photograph) (Folder M493)
    - White House delegation, 1915 Mar. 23, 1916, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M494)
      A negative was removed to N13 in the Negatives Series.
    - White House delegation, 1915 Mar. 23, 1916, (negative)
      Removed from M494 to the Negatives Series.
    - Wilson, Ben. F., 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M495)
    - Wilson, J. Stitt, 1900s, (black-and-white photographic illustration) (Folder M496)
    - Wisconsin State Socialist legislators, circa 1930, circa 1930, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M497)
    - Woodward, William E., 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M498)
    - Work, John M., 1904 July 25, 1956 June 8-10, (2 black-and-white photographs and 1 card photograph) (Folder M499)
    - Zeidler, Frank, 1956 June 8-10, 1900s, (6 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M500.1)
    - Zeidler, Frank, 1900s, (4 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M500.2)
  - Socialist Party Records Oversize Subseries, 1900-1970 and 1900s
    - Unity Convention, 1957, 1957 (Ovsz. Folder 32), (1 black-and-white photograph) (Box M01)
      Removed from M351.1-9 to the Oversize Series.
    - [Chicago] National Headquarters of Socialist Party March 1919-October 1920, 1919 Mar.-1920 Oct. (Ovsz. Folder 33), (card photograph) (Box M01)
      The negative attached to this print was removed to N7 in the Negatives Series.
    - Ameringer, Oscar, 1900s (Ovsz. Folder 34), (card photograph) (Box M01)
    - Debs, Eugene Victor, 1908 (Ovsz. Folder 35), (card photograph) (Box M01)
      Removed from M379.2 to the Oversize Series.
    - Debs, Eugene Victor [portraits and group shots], 1900s (Ovsz. Folder 36), (2 black-and-white photographs) (Box M01)
      Removed to the Oversize Subseries from M380.4.
    - Friedman, Samuel, 1900s (Ovsz. Folder 37), (sketch) (Box M01)
    - Goebel, George H., 1900s (Ovsz. Folder 38), (2 black-and-white photographs) (Box M01)
    - Hogan, Daniel, 1900s (Ovsz. Folder 39), (card photograph) (Box M01)
    - Maynard, R. A., and Mila (Tupper) Maynard, 1900s (Ovsz. Folder 40), (1 card photograph and 1 black-and-white photograph) (Box M01)
    - Mitchell, Henry Leland, 1970 Apr. 14 (Ovsz. Folder 41), (black-and-white photographic illustration) (Box M01)
    - National Executive Committee, Social Democratic Party, 1900, 1900 (Ovsz. Folder 42), (card photograph) (Box M01)
      A negative of this print was removed to N8 in the Negatives Series.
    - Thomas, Norman Mattoon (individual), 1900s (Ovsz. Folder 43), (2 card photographs and 1 black-and-white illustration) (Box M01)
      Removed to the Oversize Subseries from M485.5.
- People Series, 1700s, 1714-1974, 1900s and undated, (22 boxes)
  Making up about two-thirds of the Picture File collection, the People Series contains images of individuals and groups from many historical periods, separated into alphabetical subseries to facilitate access. The individuals depicted in this series come from widely different backgrounds, ranging from an unnamed peddler with his pack to famous Shakespearean actors. However, the majority of the images depict prominent American and European (mostly British) men, such as political and/or military leaders, clergymen, and nobles. A large portion of the American individuals portrayed in this series are Civil War commanders, both Union and Confederate. The Duke family of Durham, NC is also well-represented in the material. In addition to the alphabetical subseries, arranged chiefly by last names, this series also contains two much smaller subseries focused specifically on Native Americans) and African Americans. The terms "Negroes" and "Indians" as used in the original Picture File collection have been retained for series titles as representative of the language used in their time; cross-references have been added within the box lists under "African Americans" and "Native Americans."
  Individual portraits make up the vast majority of items in this series. While most of these pictures are posed, there is a significant number of informal images as well as large gatherings of unidentified people. photographs and engravings make up the largest group of formats in the series, though there are also lithographs, photostats, clippings, various printed illustrations, tintypes, handbills, broadsides, sketches, and postcards. Some of the more unusual genres include a souvenir menu and a page from a scrapbook. In addition, some items were separated from the main collection to allow for better housing; these include cased images, negatives, stereographs, and oversized materials. All items are arranged alphabetically (the subseries "Negroes" and "Indians" are found within this alphabetical order).
  - A-H, 1700s, 1714-1974, 1900s and undated
    - Abbott, John, circa 1870, (colored lithograph) (Box 15, Folder M501)
    - Adams, John, 1800s, (1 engraving and 1 black-and-white illustration) (Folder M502)
      Illustration taken from Jones: Biographical Sketches of the Delegates from Georgia to the Continental Congress.
    - Adams, John Quincy, undated, (engraving) (Folder M503)
    - Addington, Henry, First Viscount Sidmouth, undated, (engraving) (Folder M504)
      "Transferred from British Autographs."
    - Addison, Joseph, 1719 June 17, (engraving) (Folder M505)
    - African Americans (see "Negroes")
    - Aikman, William, undated, (engraving) (Folder M506)
    - Alcott, Amos Bronson, undated, (postcard) (Folder M507)
    - Alderman, Edwin Anderson, 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M508)
    - D' Alembert, Jean le Rond, undated, (engraving) (Folder M509)
    - Alexander II, Czar of Russia, 1800s, (2 card photographs) (Folder M510)
    - Alexander III, Czar of Russia, 1800s, (2 card photographs) (Box 16, Folder M511)
    - Alexandra, Caroline Maria Charlotte..., undated, (card photograph) (Folder M512)
      "Princess of Wales and wife of King Edward VII, King of England."
    - Alfonso XIII, King of Spain, 1904 Apr. 21, (postcard) (Folder M513)
    - Allen, Edward, undated, (card photograph) (Folder M514)
    - Allen, Edward J., undated, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M515)
    - Allen, Wm. Hervey, II, 1896 Mar. 14, (card photograph) (Folder M516)
    - Allen, Wm. Hervey, Jr., May 1895, (2 card photographs) (Folder M517)
    - Allston, Washington, 1863, (engraving) (Folder M518)
    - Amherst, William Pitt, Earl Amherst of Arracan, 1829, (engraving) (Folder M519)
    - Amos, Mose, undated, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M520)
    - Anderson, Robert H., undated, (engraving) (Folder M521)
    - Andre, Major, 1856, (engraving) (Folder M522)
    - Andrew, James O., undated, (engraving) (Folder M523)
    - Andrews, C. C., undated, (engraving) (Folder M524)
    - Angier, Malbourn Addison, 1884 and 1800s, (1 black-and-white photograph and 1 card photograph) (Folder M525)
    - Anne, Queen of Great Britain and Ireland, undated, (engraving) (Folder M526)
    - Anne, Queen of Great Britain and Ireland, 1714, (engraving) (Folder M527)
    - Anne, Second Queen of Henry VIII, 1829 May 1, (engraving) (Folder M528)
    - Aram, Eugene, undated, (black-and-white illustration) (Folder M529)
    - Ariosto, Lodovico (1474-1533), undated, (engraving) (Folder M530)
    - Arnold, Benedict, 1874, (engraving) (Folder M531)
    - Arthur, Chester Alan, undated, (engraving) (Folder M532)
    - Asbury, Francis, 1784 Dec. 27, (black-and-white illustration) (Folder M533)
    - Ashe, Samuel A'Court, undated, (2 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M534)
      Negative available.
    - Audubon, John James, 1861, (engraving) (Folder M535)
    - Augur, Christopher Columbus, undated, (engraving) (Folder M536)
    - Austin, William, undated, (engraving) (Folder M537)
    - Averell, William Woods, undated, (engraving) (Folder M538)
    - Averill, John Thomas, undated, (card photograph) (Folder M539)
    - Avery, Isaac Erwin, 1909 Feb. 2, (postcard) (Folder M540)
    - Aycock, Charles Brantley, undated, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M541)
    - Back, Sir George, undated, (card photograph) (Folder M542)
    - Bacon, A. O., undated, (card photograph) (Folder M543)
    - Bacon, John, 1815 Feb. 1, (engraving) (Folder M544)
    - Bacon, Sir Nicholas (1509-1579), 1826 Oct. 1, (engraving) (Folder M545)
    - Bailey, Christopher Thomas, undated, (card photograph) (Folder M546)
    - Bailey, James Hinton Pou, Jan. 1942, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M547)
    - Bailey, Josiah William (1873-1946), 1937, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M548)
    - Bailey, Josiah William (1873-1946), 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M549)
    - Bailhache, John and Elizabeth, undated, (2 black-and-white photostats (Folder M550)
    - Baines, Edward (1774-1848), 1834, (engraving) (Folder M551)
    - Baines, Sir Edward, undated, (engraving) (Folder M552)
    - Baird, Sir David (1757-1829), 1833, (engraving) (Folder M553)
    - Baldwin, Abraham, 1888, (2 engravings) (Folder M554)
      One engraving is from Jones: Biog. Sketches of the Delegates from Georgia to the Continental Congress.
      One is signed by Abraham Baldwin.
    - Baldwin, Briscoe G., undated, (engraving) (Folder M555)
      Brittle original: use photocopy in folder.
    - Balfour, Arthur James, undated, (black-and-white photographic illustration) (Folder M556)
      Reproduction of a photograph transferred from British Autographs.
    - Ball, William Watts, 1925 and 1900s, (5 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M557)
    - Ball William Watts, 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M558)
    - Bancroft, George, undated, (engraving) (Folder M559)
    - Banks, Nathaniel Prentice, undated, (engraving) (Folder M560)
    - Barbour, Philip P., 1889, (sketch) (Folder M561)
    - Barden, Graham Arthur, 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M562)
    - Barlow, Joel, undated, (engraving) (Folder M563)
    - Barlow, W. Warren, 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M564)
    - Barton, Stephen R., undated, (2 card photographs) (Folder M565)
    - Bartow, Francis S., undated, (engraving) (Folder M566)
    - Bartram, William, undated, (engraving) (Folder M567)
    - Baruch, B. M., 1918 Dec. 20, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M568)
    - Battle, William, undated, (card photograph) (Folder M569)
    - Beale, Richard L[ee] T[urberville], 1800s, (black-and-white photographic illustration) (Folder M570)
    - Beasley, William Fessenden, 1800s, (2 card photographs) (Folder M571)
    - Beauregard, Pierre Gustave Toutant, 1865, 1800s and undated, (3 card photographs, 1 black-and-white photograph and 2 engravings) (Folder M572)
      One item signed by Beauregard.
    - Bedford, Gunning (1747-1812), undated, (engraving) (Folder M573)
    - Bedinger, Carolina Bowne (Lawrence), undated, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M574)
      A negative was removed to N14 in the Negatives Series.
    - Bedinger, Carolina Bowne (Lawrence), undated, (negative)
      Removed from M574 to the Negatives Series.
    - Bee, Frederick A. and Katie M., 1883 May 9 and 1800s, (2 card photographs) (Folder M575)
    - Beecher, John, 1974 Apr., (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M576)
    - Beecher, Lyman, undated, (engraving) (Folder M577)
    - Benjamin, Judah Philip, undated, (2 engravings) (Folder M578)
    - Benson, Joseph, undated, (engraving) (Folder M579)
    - Benson, W. S., undated, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M580)
    - Bentham, Jeremy, undated, (engraving) (Folder M581)
    - Benton, Thomas Hart, 1862, 1864 and 1800s, (3 engravings) (Folder M582)
    - Berrien, John McPherson, undated, (2 engravings) (Folder M583)
      One of these engravings is from the Geo. Hist. Society.
    - Bismarck-Schönhausen, von Otto Eduard Leopold, 1880, (card photograph) (Folder M584)
    - Bismarck-Schönhausen, von Otto Eduard Leopold, undated, (postcard) (Folder M585)
    - Blackwell, James L., and Blackwell, Eleanor Fox (Buchanan), undated, (3 card photographs) (Folder M586)
    - Blackwell, William Thomas, undated, (card photograph) (Folder M587)
    - Blackwell, William Thomas, undated, (card photograph) (Folder M588)
    - Blair, John (Signers of Constitution), 1890, (engraving) (Folder M589)
    - Blake, Robert (1599-1657), circa 1836, (3 engravings) (Folder M590)
    - Blanchard, Newton, undated, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M591)
    - Blount, Charles, Earl of Devonshire..., undated, (engraving) (Folder M592)
    - Blount, William (1744-1800), undated, (engraving) (Folder M593)
    - Boccaccio, Giovanni, undated, (engraving) (Folder M594)
    - Bocock, Thomas Stanley, undated, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M595)
    - Bodley, Sir Thomas, 1823 Jan. 1, (engraving)
      Removed to Folder OV44, Box M02, Oversize Subseries.
    - Böcklin, Arnold, undated, (postcard) (Box 17, Folder M596)
    - Boggs, William Robertson, circa 1860s and 1800s, (2 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M597)
    - Bonaparte, Napoleon, undated, (card photograph) (Folder M598)
      Photograph of a painting by Isabey. See also M1790 in the People Series for an additional engraving.
    - Bonaparte, Napoleon II..., 1828 Jan. 1, (engraving)
      Removed to Folder OV45, Box M02, Oversize Subseries.
    - Bonaparte, Napoleon, and family, undated, (12 postcards) (Folder M599.1)
      See also M1790 in the People Series for an additional engraving.
    - Bonaparte, Napoleon, and family, undated, (12 postcards) (Folder M599.2)
    - Bonaparte, Napoleon, and family, undated, (3 postcards) (Folder M599.3)
    - Bonner, Herbert Covington, 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M600)
      Transferred from the Graham Arthur Barden Papers.
    - Boone, Daniel, 1861, (engraving) (Folder M601)
    - Booth, Edwin, 1800s, (card photograph) (Folder M602)
      From the C. C. Clay Mss.
    - Booth, John Wilkes, 1800s, (card photograph) (Folder M603)
    - Boudinot, Elias, 1820, (engraving) (Folder M604)
    - Bradford, Gamaliel, 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M605)
    - Bragg, Braxton, undated, (2 engravings and 1 card photograph) (Folder M606)
    - Branch-Cunningham Families, 1866 Feb.-1885 and 1800s, (10 card photographs and 1 tintype) (Folder M607.1)
    - Branch-Cunningham Families, 1867 Mar. 29-1883 Mar. 24 and 1800s, (12 card photographs) (Folder M607.2)
    - Branch-Cunningham Families, 1869-1881 Feb. 25 and 1800s, (11 card photographs) (Folder M607.3)
    - Branch-Cunningham Families, 1860-1883 Mar. 14 and 1800s, (10 card photographs) (Folder M607.4)